I don't know if I can do this, but I can do this.
Oh
I don't know what you're talking
Speaker 2: about.
Speaker 2: I
don't think he's going to do the same thing!
Speaker 2: He's going to do the same thing! He's going to do
Speaker 3: the same thing! He's going to do the same thing! He's going
to do the
Speaker 3: same thing!
He's going to do the same thing! He's going to do
Speaker 5: the same thing! He's going
to do the
Speaker 5: same thing! He's going to do the same thing! He's going to do the same thing! He's going
to do the same thing! He's going
Speaker 8: to do the same thing! He's going to do the same thing! Come
Speaker 7: on,
lock on!
Speaker 8: I
Speaker 9: don't
Speaker 11: know what
Speaker 12: you're
Speaker 14: talking
Speaker 15: about.
Speaker 18: I
don't know what you're doing but I don't know what you're doing. I don't know what
Speaker 19: you're doing. I don't
know what
Speaker 20: you're doing.
Speaker 19: I don't know
what you're doing. I don't
Speaker 19: know what you're doing. I don't know
what you're
Speaker 19: doing. I don't know what you're
Speaker 22: doing.
I don't know what you're doing. I don't know
Speaker 23: what you're doing.
I don't
Speaker 24: know what you're doing. I don't know what you're doing. I don't know what you're doing. I don't know what you're
Speaker 25: doing. I don't know what you're doing. I don't
know what
Speaker 25: you're doing. I don't know what you're doing. I
Speaker 26: don't know what you're doing. I don't know what you're doing. I don't know
what you're doing.